ppz.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy & Security | PPZ.COM

This privacy policy explains what personal information is collected through this Web site, how that information is used, to whom it's disclosed, and how it's safeguarded. Unless indicated otherwise, this policy applies only to personal information collected through the Web site of PPZ, By "personal information" we mean your identifying information (like name, home address, and email address), and descriptive information (like tastes and preferences) if coupled with your identifying information. We may refer to PPZ as "we," "us," or "our" throughout this privacy policy.

 **This privacy policy answers these questions**  

What personal information is collected and how is it used?

How do we secure your information on our site?

Where is personal information stored and processed?

When was this policy last updated?

 **What personal information is collected and how is it used?**

We collect personal information directly from Web sites, such as name, address, phone number, email address, personal preferences, credit card number, purchase and ordering information, responses to survey questions and sizing information. This information is collected at various places on our site: for instance, when you check out 

with your online order; subscribe to catalogs, and email offers.  

 _We use personal information to do things like_

  * process your online orders

  * open an online account at your request

  * provide customer service, whether it's responding to a request or following up on an order

  * include you in surveys and contests

  * enable you to post your content, such as comments or images

  * facilitate networks of online social activity centered around our products and services

  * improve our website, improve the manner in which offers are made on our website, improve purchase decisions of our visitors and the interactions visitors have with our website

 **How we use the information we collect?**

Our Web site has the following types of security measures: limited access data-centers, firewall technology, and (for our e-Commerce sites through which you may place orders) secure-socket-layer (SSL) certificate authentication. SSL is encryption technology that provides security for information that's transmitted over the Internet.  

While we implement the above security measures on our site, you should be aware that 100% security is not always possible.  

We will not sell or share your personal information or email. Your information is only used to complete your order and for marketing purposes, if you have opted for this feature.  

 **Where is personal information stored and processed?**

PPZ Inc. is a global organization, with affiliated legal entities, business processes, management structures, and technical systems that cross borders. As the majority of our administrative and technical support functions are headquartered in the US we share, store and process personal information in the United States of America. Customers accessing and purchasing with our sales website will be interacting with servers and services provided from within the United States of America.  

We may share or store your personal information among PPZ Inc. brands and transfer it to our business partners based in various countries in the world where we do business.  

When we transfer your personal information internationally we will take steps to ensure that your personal information is treated lawfully in the manner we describe in this privacy policy.  

 **When was this policy last updated?**

This Privacy Statement is effective February 12, 2015.
